Hello Trader this is Manas welcome back to our
channel this is ICICI
GI 12 month time frame you can see that
from the down side parallel trend line is being
shown forming towards the upside on which
taking support momentum is being shown towards the upside you
can see on the upside of the parallel trend line you can see breakout of trend line level in previous
and on recent you will see
zone levels being shown forming
on the down side and from the upside trend line
triangle pattern is being shown forming, we will
wait for the breakout to happen.
On the weekly time frame, you will see
zone levels forming in the middle.   The
zone levels on the upside are
important horizontal levels on the downside.
So you will see that
if there is a breakout at the 90 level of 19.15 then we
can plan the trade with the breakout of the trend line level.
In which our stop loss
level will be 18879.45 and your target level
will be
zone levels
from 2037.90 to 2074.50.
After that your zone levels will be from
262.85 to
23100.90 on the upside.
And if rejection is seen from this level,
then you can plan a trade on the downside at the
level of 1794.95, in which you will keep the stop loss level, in this the
target level will be 1837.45,
your downside zone levels will be
1696.70,
next target up to 1607.40,
on the daily time frame you will see that the trend
line is becoming monthly, from upside to downside
and is also being formed from the downside.
If the triangle pattern breaks out,
you can plan a trade.   You
can plan a trade at the level of 1915.90.
With the breakout, the stop loss level will be
1983.80,
target level will be 1976.70,
next target will be 2036.40.
After that you will see that if there is a
breakdown on the downside then you can plan the trade, your
stop loss level will be at the level of 1765.85 and
target level will be 1793.50, your zone
levels will be at the
one hour time frame of 1693.90, you will see that the double top has
closed.  First top second top
on 15 minute time frame you will see breakdown of
trend line level from down side to upside, you
can plan the trade.
Stop loss level will be at 1824.230,
target level will be 1837.75, next target will be 1800.70, next target
will be 1765.85.  So you should trade only after maintaining your risk reward
ratio and
taking advice from a financial advisor.  Thank
you so much for watching the video till the end.